apc.org 2018-06-29

# Privacy policy | Association for Progressive Communications

This policy outlines the methods that we use to collect, share and protect any personally identifiable information in offline and online settings. This website, APC.org, follows this policy and applicable laws in the country where it is stored, the United Kingdom.

###### Collecting information

Website statistics: We collect the date, time and length of your visit, browser identification and IP address for internal use and analysis of website traffic. This information is anonymised and used for statistical analysis only.

Website cookies: We use the necessary cookies to make the website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website.

Email sign-up to our newsletter: When you provide us with your email address to receive newsletter updates at that email address, we use this internally and never share it with others. We will confirm your consent to receive the newsletters regularly, at least every 12 months.

Other personal information: We don't collect your information without your permission. We don't use your information without your permission.

###### Sharing information

We never sell or rent your information.

We do not share your information with anyone outside APC, and to ensure this we avoid the use of third-party services on our website. We will only disclose personal information that we possess (whether about staff, contacts or anyone else) where compelled by law.

###### Protecting information

Information in transit: Our websites use encrypted protocols to receive any information you share with us and for information that our website sends back to you.

Information at rest: Any information such as website statistics or personally identifiable information that you have willingly shared with us is protected with encryption on our servers.

###### Other applicable policies

If you want to obtain a copy of any personal information about you that we have in our systems, please write to [privacy@apc.org](mailto:privacy@apc.org).

If you want us to delete personal information about you that we have stored in our systems, please write to [privacy@apc.org](mailto:privacy@apc.org).

This website is hosted by GreenNet. Therefore, their Code of Practice is also relevant and can be found [here](http://www.greennet.org.uk/about/code-practice).

Our supervisory authority on data privacy is the UK’s Information Commissioner’s Office ([ICO](https://ico.org.uk/))

_Active policy updated May 2018._
